The invention project of the Inventor Dragon Team: lead the high-explosive situation of the dam. The reason is in the game,
The insurance and room cards you purchase by yourself have a very low explosion rate, and you often lose money.
So our inventor studied in isolation, and finally developed a method to distinguish 大红, which is very easy to use.
When entering the game first, open the map to see if there are any wall-breaking tasks, and remember these combinations.
First of all, there is the Deng Ling Jia Jin Cup, which is a must-see for the various containers and man-machine boxes of the Dai Jin Bureau.
Especially the broken soldiers and machine gunners. Information mid-end plus.
The turkey is a combination of goldenrod. There are so many goldenrods that you must scrape the ground clean. Gold bars and lanterns,
Absolutely 大红ju can grab insurance and open a card, guaranteeing you a guaranteed profit without any loss.
Finally, there are the studio plus medals and champagne plus gold coins. The explosion rate is very low, just touch it and evacuate.
Then Team Dragon will share a little trick with you: let the machine shoot you twice at the beginning, and you will be beaten to half health.
Just open the card with all your strength. Inventing direction, No. 0 has a lot of high-explosive chrysanthemums, success.